Swapnil Suresh Maindre

CIVIL ENGINEER



About Me



2 Year experience



7769888901



swapnilmaindre21@gmail.com



Profile

2 years of civil engineering Architectural Planning, construction, quality control and management experience in residential, commercial and industrial projects. Capable of working independently with minimum supervision, and committed to providing high quality service to every project, with focus on health, safety and environmental issues. Professional, capable, and motivated individual who consistently performs in challenging environments. Possess near about 1 years of experience in Revit modeling. Make the Career in BIM work with such a firm where I can used my theory knowledge and learn professional aspects of these field in least time with professional atmosphere so I can serve for the society in younger age by designing various structures. I have experience in BIM (Building Information Modeling) Architecture & Structure.



Education

Degree: People's Education Society, Aurangabad. (2018 - 2021)

CGPA:- 8.26

Diploma: MGM's Polytechnic, Aurangabad. (2014 - 2018)

Percentage:-66.36 %



Professional Experience

□ RPROJECT ENGINEER At

At IAS & Associates, Aurangabad, Maharashtra. (September 2021- Ongoing)

Roles & Responsibilities (September 2021- Ongoing)
• Checking concrete quality before casting, Keeping note of each & every casting

- work and other work.

 Prepare NOC, As-Built and Working drawing of proposed petrol pump.
- Doing valuation site visits and Prepare Report.
- Doing marking and leveling of petrol pump as per drawing on site.
- Doing site visit for Feasibility, NOC and NH Permission and prepare report.
- Prepare BOQ, RA Bill and Final Bill as per actual measurements.
- Strong co-ordination skills that help in liaising of NH , NOC files.

☐ Jr. DESIGN ENGINEE

At Infinity & Associates, Aurangabad, Maharashtra.

□ Roles & Responsibilities

(February 2021 to July 2021)

- prepare submission drawings and documents of residential building for building permission.
- Consulted with architects and clients to ensure the proper materials and layouts were being implemented to achieve safety, functionality and efficiency.
- Prepare structural drawing of residential, Commercial and Industrial Structure.
- Doing valuation site visits and Prepare Report.
- •Create 3d BIM models of structural & architecture of building. Edit models based on engineer instructions. Create plans, sections, details, quantity schedules for documentation. Generate drawings, pdfs, dwgs or images from model formats. Follows firm and project document standards.
- Provide CAD drafting/BIM modeling and design support. Create Revit families and CAD blocks.



Internship & Training

- Trainee site Engineer at 'Vikas Developers' Aurangabad.
- Completed 'Advanced BIM' Course at D & D Engineering Institute, Aurangabad.



• SOFTWARE SKILLS & PROFESSIONALY TRAINED

- AutoCAD
- NAVISWORKS
- BIM
- Revit Architecture
- Revit Structure
- Revit MEP
- Revit HVAC
- STAAD PRO
- MS OFFICE
- QUANTITY SURVEY
- TOTAL STATION

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH
- HINDI
- MARHATI

STREENGTH

- Ability to work Individually as well as Team
- Time Management
- Quick Learner
- Adaptable

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birthday :-20/08/1998 Marital Status :-Single Gender :- Male Nationality :- INDIAN Address :- N-12,

D-5/7,Hudco,

Aurangabad. (431001)